be successful in the stock market,
you will have to stay updated and for that you will have to
join my Telegram channel
whose link I have given in my description box
where I take a
screenshot of every share I like for you
within 2 minutes and now I am going to give this
facility to YouTube subscribers soon, that is, I will
share the screenshot of every share I like on my YouTube channel, for that you will have to
subscribe to my YouTube channel and
it is absolutely free and you will have to keep the notification bar
on so that whatever screenshot of the share I
put on YouTube, you will
see it on your screen, so please
subscribe my YouTube channel
friends, welcome to your own family
channel Stock Analysis in Hindi, how are
you today I have brought some great strokes for you
and this non stop is
a kind of Navaratna stock which in itself is
excellent, I always try to
introduce you the right stock at the right price, before you must have seen
I told you about Zee Entertainment, Sona, BMW, Mannapuram
Finance, IX, Laxmi Organic, India
Diction Technology, IRCTC, Asian
Paints, many such shares
and today all these 30  There has been a
rise of like 200 percent, on which
I had told about many shares more than 50-60, on
which I had told, from
there you must have seen that there has been a rise of 30 percent to
200 to 300,
which I tell you to do at this level, I have
brought an important topic for you, in
which if you want, you can
buy according to your interest, because
I feel
Meghnad
that all these stocks can collapse anytime and you should always see that the
famous price is a good price,
otherwise it is not, nowadays you will see any price of the price, you have started trading, whichever stock you
enter, it goes to this topic, brother,
right now it seems that where we are in the stock,
it does not run at all, Ajay, the market is moving like this,
but someday someone's
valuation will come, when there will be a strange elevation, then when you
buy at a high level, it should not happen that in the current
situation, when you open the app and it falls from there,
then you do not get it up quickly, this should not happen, that is
why we should
prepare it in such a way that where there is a good price  If there is an
available undergraduate share and the
market falls here, then there should
not be much fall in this share. I
already have stocks with you. You must have
seen that the shares have increased a lot in the market.
Now there is no benefit in entering that market. If
possible, it
can show more growth from here. Those who have increased by
300 percent, if they want,
they can increase by 100 percent, but there is
no benefit in that if you fall further, then
we will suffer loss, a lot of loss can be seen.
That is why my effort is
always that when a good share
reaches a good level, then see the fun at that time, see
how much fun it is when the share goes further
and there is a lot of fun in earning profit. Now it is
your choice whether you
want to invest in any of these stocks and which
stock you want to avoid. Along with this, I will also
tell you at which level it can be traded and at
which level one should not trade or can be
avoided. I am going to
tell you all this in detail in today's video, so
you should watch this video completely.  Watch carefully,
look carefully at the stock
that I am telling you about, see about that city,
you will be targeting that this set is
not being formed, I am going to tell you all this in this video,
along with that I will also
tell you that there is time to come in this hair,
how much future can be made, before this if
you are watching my video for the first time then do
not forget to subscribe to our channel, like and share our channel,
please do subscribe to our channel so that you can get
quality videos on time,
along with this keep pressing the icon bell button
so that whatever video I upload,
you can get it on time, along with this I have given my
Telegram channels in my description box,
you can go there and join, I keep
talking about many such shares, I keep
sharing its screenshot,
you can go and see it on my team channel,
let's start the program with
this stock analysis in Hindi, the
first stock that I have brought is Times,
you must have seen this stock, it has been surrounded for a long time, it has been
falling continuously for some time, it was made for a fixed period
only, after that there has been a continuous
fall here, he got married in October and
I had done business there  I had applied for it and I got it
too and I booked 50% profit there,
I always do 50% profit whenever it comes and
when it is launched and there is profit, I
leave 50% in front, when its
launch was listed, its share had fallen to a great extent
and
I bought a lot here around 13th and it seemed that it had
gone up to around 38,
from there also it had gone up by 200,
around thousand, the 13th chapter milk which I had bought, I have
kept something there at any time but you must have
seen that
I have fixed at a good time around 3000 at 3231 gas,
this falling woman, I will
buy more, the share is quite good for the future, that is,
if you are a long term
investor, then you can
buy this stock even at this current price, the market price is quite
good, the price is quite attractive,
why now see, we will take
out its 468, it is worth ₹12100,
so this is your calculation  It has
given a good correction of about one thousand rupees.
This correction of one thousand rupees is not less, that is,
after making a very fast rally,
this channel has given a good correction, you
will see that it had made a good rally here
and after this we will go to this point, it has
given a good correction from here, so
after giving such a good collection of 1000,
if Bhindi has not been able to do so, then what can be said
that Shekhar, nothing can happen, so
if you want to grow here, then
definitely make a little entry and if I
talk about the World Bank, then you can tweet this layer, if it is a
long term investment, then someone is listening,
if you want to stop for a while, then
you can go up to 2800 27 in the i button, it
is a little difficult but if you go, then
definitely do bank here and on this
lever also you keep on releasing
something or the other in Metro Delhi, even today, during the
festival, it keeps falling and falling, that is why
I keep buying something or the other in Delhi
and I will also bulk pack it here
in the coming time, the app and it will come to
you soon  It will show black around 35.
Once this stock touches or crosses the level of 32, then
this stock will touch the naval of f-35 in the coming time
and will keep it there for some time, for
a year, that you will see four or plus.
I think the stock can
go up to ₹45 or even ₹100 in the coming time. I think it can go up to 50% from here.
I don't want to
talk about diet, it can go up to 269 also.
I think the
other stock is Alembic Pharma,
I had made a video of it many times. I had also bought
its stock, I thought it was
around 740 here, it was quite good here.
I had bought it from here, it was one and a half inch. I have
brought its graph today that you
will see that this stock gave a very high return in one day,
friend, but this is not its price, it is
much more than this, well it has
given a correction, it is
around the makers negatives, so from my right hand itself, the
crush here is very high, almost more than ₹300.
But
Bhavanik Shampoo has already given a correction and I had made a
good buy here at 835 around 740, there is
still an opportunity here,
not much time has passed to enter this stock,
I think that after crossing the 850 level,
this stock will be your
target at 95015 and next, this stock of this date
plus rate should be bought quickly, that is,
you can see it reaching 1000 plus in itself,
I think this is a
very good collection of Shade 300, which is a
batting correction in the pharma industry
and this is a very good
quarter guard, the previous quarter clear was
bad, in this a lot of decline is seen in the stock,
sometimes the quarter
back clear becomes bad due to which there is a
decline, but I cannot give such a pump reminder,
this stock cannot show a rise in the time of coming
because if you do it now then it has
not gone, let us talk about the NAC in
ICICI Lombard General Insurance,
in this sector, I always
think this time is very good for swing trading, that is, you will
see that when  It is also said that it makes a move and
then falls from there and then it
rises again and then it falls again and then it rises again and
then it rises again and
this move is against the government
and a situation of division of 1675 is formed here
and then from there you can see that there has been a
fall here of 1675, you will see that
different levels of 155 have
shown a good fall here, I said that there has been a
good correction at 155 here,
I thought this is a very good time, if possible,
I think if this stock falls from here, then
I think this stock can go up to 1440, you should
start buying on this level and
start doing something, if any
long-term investor wants, then he can
start buying and if 1440 becomes
1420, then it can also be banked, it is a
very good stock, in future once
this stock crosses the level of against 1600,
it will give you a
class advantage for Vitamin Kshatrapas  It can be seen around in the
coming time, so I think this share can
cross the ₹70 level here within 3-4 minutes, from
here you can see good money and profit,
so I think that is why buy from here
and if it comes around 1420 to 1440 then
bulk pack can also be done with this,
come on the NAAC Varun
Beverage Swarnarekha, I had
made a video of many when it was coming around 720 730
some time ago and I had
also said that at this 730 I had
bulk packed 720p 73466 for the bank and if they wanted,
when they sent the symbol on them, you have
seen friends, there was a good profit of 230
here, I myself had
bulk packed here around 725 today
and I felt that I had sold a lot of shares here around Note Shop 40,
right now a
lot of my shares are read even after selling,
but now I want to re-
enter here for 897 also  This is the current market
price, so the search can be continued.
This is a mid-cap company, the risks of the model-actress are
very less, it is not that
much, its risk is low and quite good.
I find this to be my favorite stock. Now
you are feeling that I may have
made six buys in a range, it is remaining
in the same range in a single day,
but once this stock starts moving,
then it is out of your hands or
you can do nothing except regret.
You are also thinking that why we are not getting Tata Motors,
whereas
friends, run Tata Motors at 80, Jatin Boss-8,
if it got 280, then there will be no link
during the decline in the village of Lecturer,
but today people are ready to buy even at 500 plus,
why brother, when it came to 280, then
why were you people not buying and now you are saying
that we are ready for 500, different things, this is the same
thing that happens that when the department goes,
people who buy at high level and then get ruined, then it is
better than that, or better than that
When the fundamentals are better than its family, then
you should buy it whether it is at any discount level or not, you should
not think and
should leave it for the future, all these shares will give
you very good returns,
I believed that it is your choice whether you want to
buy it or not, it is your money,
you have to invest your money, you have to take the decision, so
you must have written
mi6, the share of M.Ed DSC Life Insurance
Company, you must have seen that I have brought the
graph of this in the village, now some time
ago it had made a modern high of 775, it is 775,
you will see it, it must have looked good, it has made a
good correction of Rs. 75 here,
till today also, today the
Beloved Country has closed with a fall of six percent
and today the
hybrid which had made a laugh at 709, again
Urmila's share is very good,
start buying here, once
it runs again, cross the level of 775,
this share you should take in the top 50  It will be
visible around us, it takes a little time in
all this in the stock, that is, when there are devotees
who run fast, but what happens is that they stop after
coming to a content,
I have now seen it mostly
between 675 to 725, it could happen in a period
here, if we turn towards the
murder, that is,
it will remain stuck between the level of 675 to 725 and as this stock
works at the level of 740 to 750,
you can also see it touching 825 Jhalevar,
so I think the current market
price is Rs.700, you should definitely buy here,
hence the stock falls and can
come between 650 to 675 anytime,
rather like it and it is very good
in the coming time that you will see tremendous benefits,
they have treatment but even the text of 1950,
our risk is very low, it is Road East Africa
and you should see the best shares and brands of the insurance sector,
HDFC Bank is
a great brand in itself, it is a good brand, it is good
Hair oil Comedy 16th has
shown a lot of decline here, you will see that its one year old
father said that after falling from 800 rupees, a
lot of correction can be seen here,
about 200 ₹70 has been
captured at 280 77270, a kind of correction has been seen,
which collection of ₹70 does
not decrease, that is, you will see that this stock
started running from here and stopped at 816
and from there it remains content in a joint
and then it
falls from there, I think that once this stock
crosses the level of 625, this
stock will again torch and go towards 800, there should be
control time, I have just given assurance
of ₹500 in the stock, which was released a day or two ago,
but I had
bought it at 5745, this stock falls further from here,
I will play here again, it is a
very good stock and it is a product
free company and the stock is quite great, so
you should buy this hair oil here a
little  All the time if this stock
crosses 600 caliber here it
can show you the labor of breathing around 6 hokies
try to find out quickly I feel that what is said about the
NAC stock is wrong that Berger
Paints paint statement is an excellent stock
I had issued its statement of 784
I have also made a video when it came around 784
and I had also bought and
you will see that it jumped and I am getting good profit
but right now you will see that it is
stuck here in the same danger for four-five months it is stuck between about 700 to 750
to 840 I think
most of the people who will come till the last man on Diwali and Anup Shukla can also touch it
in their hair which
is above 872, cross it there it
can go towards 90950 it is a very good
stock you will see its returns but
according to this but
what is the best relation of 40 per cent, in 5 years it has been
almost suppressed in this city  209 Karthika has given a return of 200%
here, it is a
very good city, you will see that Sharma has
given a good profit of 36 percent,
so I think on the coming Diwali it will
make you a good profit from here and so even at this current level you
can prepare, listen, this is for the long term,
so definitely stay in this, it is
not that you will always get Tata and
Tata Motors because of Tata and they will always keep
running, once you buy a share, you
feel that our share has started falling
and especially see, you feel lazy, then this should
not happen, you have confidence in your hair, that is,
how is the share you are buying, you will have to judge it yourself,
buy in any share, the
next one is Sara Limited, Chemical,
ATM, Shutter, it is an excellent share, it is a state
company, I bought it for some time now,
so I always keep buying it
in swing trading and lots of readings and
I like this very much, you just saw that this share had
reached 12000 there  There was a
spirit from there and from there the speed was quite good here, okay
here it is around 2465 rupees,
here the challan Babuni why did it have 2538
and there has not been much correction seen,
which if you take out, the
174% return of 10 years at 857 has been good,
if there is a fall in this,
I think it is just
calibration, but if there is a fall, then even at
this level you should keep buying 12 shares,
I will not say much, I will
not advise for that line, but keep
writing for long term and there is a lot of fall here,
a question of 15% of these desperation comes, so in this channel
you can do Dua which entry can also be done in bank, if you
cannot do bulk pack,
then you can invest at least a good amount of
money in it, no, you
can put 50% of the bank's investment here on the fall of 10 to 15, a little weight that
I think Bhushan is too much,
come a little at the right time  But you can take it here, and keep
taking it from 12,
you will see tremendous profits from this hair every month. I don't
like the shares. I am talking about the
SBI card payment service. I have invested a lot this year.
You have
seen that I have joined TV channels. I
invest a lot in this
and keep earning good profits.
So, I think that at this
time I have invested at least two-three times more than that.
I have earned profit here till now.
I think so because
you will see that whenever I make my Babuni,
if I go and buy,
then as you said, I
send some shares here, keep them,
then buy, then send them. And
I have done this many times and
whenever I buy, I always keep them for long-term
tune. Well, long-
term play is also a share and to start with, I
use a separate account.
I get good profit from it.
You will see that whenever a modern
makes a move, if it goes, as Agyeya said, it
makes a move, if it falls, if it is neck-deep.  It forms
again, falls, forms a fragrance, then it starts
falling here, you see,
whenever it forms sentiments, if it falls
and then forms again, then its
falling, I think in the coming positive
it can touch the Ashoka level,
be patient, see this tremendous profit in the i button,
many purchases will be made even at the current market price, even
today I have
bought spider-man of line 996, the note is ₹10, I made a
surprise purchase of ₹
1100 here, that is why with efforts I had issued a call hungry on the forests,
today I have bought at 90,
whenever there is a fall of ten to twenty rupees,
I will keep buying, that is why I have to
listen, I have seen a good profit in the time of eating
because till now there was only
one share of the account statement, of cutter
comment, which was stable in the market, apart from that there is no other
share of the account statement,
so you see the brand, SBI is a
government company bank brand, it is
very good and their cards are also very
famous, and they bring from Next, this
is the best company in this car segment, that is, the
second largest companies, first pack  If you have
abs then camp on second section with SBI
card which is the largest Indian best
company I think this set is very
good it will give huge profits in the coming time
so can you buy at inverter price there is
no issue these were today's date no best
Navratna Siyag if you liked our video
then don't forget to subscribe our channel
please subscribe my YouTube
channel and also join our channel
so that you can get many benefits filled
in the footer you will
see there that I buy shares little by little
and along with that I keep buying shares separately
weekends I am
not able to take screenshot of it because I
rather join that because what happens is that from small to
big investors attend the camp so I don't have any flavour because
I keep telling a lot of investors to do it for 1 minute, no
one listens to me but there will be a lot of small
investors or I will drag them in and put them in
you will think that I can buy as much money as possible in the campus
because
I don't have it  Why would I
say that because of this he will not be able to play,
this is one thing that remains in the mind, that is why I do it
separately, okay, you keep
as much capital as you want with Scariest Capital, in this you keep
buying, these are notes
and best shares, rest it is your choice which
share you want to buy now, buying in cash also,
it is up to you what you want to do,
okay, if I say this then
you can buy Aajevika Dhap anytime, there
is no hearing, but these notes and
best shares can be bought in the market at any
date, so please
subscribe my YouTube channel, thank you